David Ghazaryan

Contact

Phone:

+374 (98) 262929

Email:

davidghazaryan2000@gmail.com

Website:

http://davidghazaryan.ga

Programming

JS, React JS, Node JS

PHP OOP

Bash/Shell

AppleScript

Languages

English

Russian

Armenian

Summary

Middle Web developer. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, Bash/Shell. Background in project management and customer relations. Now fully centralized on JS frameworks, especially React JS.

Experience

Full-Stack Web Developer - 04/2018 to Present - Yerevan, Armenia

Freelance - 04/2018 to 01/2019 Upwork.com, Freelancer.com

- Armenian several news sites and support for them.
- Worked with development team on entertainment news site using HTML, Sass, jQuery/UI, GIT, WebStorm, Wordpress.
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Plugins, bug fixings and Reviews.

Full Stack WEB Developer - 11/2018 to 04/2020 Astgeek, Yerevan

- Worked with large development team using for
 - Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, CSS Animation, JavaScript, jQuery/UI, SASS.
 - Back-End: PHP OOP, ElasticSearch, REDIS, DOCKER, Capistrano, NodeJS for chatbot.

Front-End Developer (remote) - 01/2019 to present **MediaSystems**, Yerevan

- Created own ads_controller to display the ads in which the user is interested. Created player which supports VAST2/3.
- Written custom js compiler/composer for these ads_controller modules.
- Designed various JavaScript mini-game advertisements.
- Developed cross-browser compatible multi-advertisement coregistration engine for ad promotions.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.

Education

Bachelor of Science:

National Polytechnic University of Armenia: remote – 2017-2022

Web & Game Development:

TUMO Gyumri: 2016-2018

High school:

Gyumri Photon Collage: 2006-2017